

Mobile/ Web Developer/Junior frontend /Full stack: I am a 26 years old developer with a passion for developing good product software. I am willing to learn and am a hard working individual only through hard work I believe in archiving once objective. I believe in team work and I love reading manga , playing chess ,exercising and playing video games. I am a great individual to have on your work force am always pushing myself to be better at everything I do .Anyways lets save the chit chat for the interview...

Lethabo Joy Lekoloane

Phone:

+27 722 430 359

E-Mail:

lethabolekoloane11@gmail.com

LinkedIn:

linkedin.com/in/Lethabo-joy-lekoloane-3003881aa

GitHub:

Github.com/lethabolekoloane

Availability:

Limpopo & Gauteng (immediately)

Skill Highlights

- Team Player
- Strong decision maker
- Complex problem solver
- Innovative & Goal driven

Languages

English(good) Sepedi(home language) Zulu / Tshivenda (good)

Education

02/2015-11/2019

BSc Mathematical science(Computer Science & Mathematic) - University of Limpopo ,RSA

01/2010-11/2014

Kgakala sec school bachelor pass

Experience

05/2021-06/2021

Figma Prototype Developer @ AgritourZA

Development of UI/UX prototypes

04/2020-03/2021

Web Developer/fullstack developer @mLabs codetribe

- Remote learner ship
- Full stack development using, AngularJS ,lonic ,firebase and figma ui/ux design

01/2020 -03/2020

Assistant Lecturer @Santon College Polokwane campus (voluntary)

• mathematics grade 12 & (N2,N3,N4,N5 and N6)

12 days (contract)

Examination Assistant @Department of Education (2018)

script marking and mark confirmation

Physics and Mathematics Tutor @TWB (grade 10 and 11) (voluntary)

Software skills

FRONTEND

- HTML(skilled)
- CSS/SCSS(skilled)
- JAVASCRIPT/OOP(skilled)
- ANGULARJS (skilled)
- IONIC(skilled)
- TYPESCRIPT(skilled)
- C++/JAVA(medium)
- PYTHON(beginner)

BACKEND/DATABASES

- FIREBASE/ NODEJS
- SQL(medium)

OTHER TOOLS

- API'S
- BOOSTRAP/CORDOVA
- ANGULAR METERIAL

UI/UX

FIGMA DESIGNS

MICROSOFT OFFICE SKILLS: MS OUTLOOK, MS WORD, MS EXCEL, MS POWERPOINT, MS ACCESS

References

References available on request